# HANK TEICHEIRA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

# CONTACT

707-695-0029



Berkeley, CA



hteicheira@gmail.com



hteichei.github.io



github.com/hteichei



linkedin.com/in/hteicheira in



# EDUCATION

RITHM SCHOOL. SF **FULL STACK ENGINEERING** Jun-Sep 2018

> **UC DAVIS B.S. VITICULTURE & ENOLOGY** 2011 - 2015

#### KEY SKILLS

JavaScript (ES6)

jQuery

React (Redux)

**React Native** 

Python

Flask

Node.js

**Express** 

**PostareSQL** 

HTML & CSS

#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a full stack software engineer with a passion for creating practical, meaningful products. I have a strong background in food, wine, and agriculture and I hope to use my experience to build and contribute to novel applications.

# EXPERIENCE

### MOBILE ENGINEER INTERN

Groupmuse / San Francisco, CA / Aug 2018

Worked in pair-programming environment on a six-person team for four weeks developing a React Native iOS mobile application under supervision of CTO.

- Implemented a key multi-step guest reservation feature in the React Native application to increase user engagement.
- Consumed RESTful API's to implement CRUD functionality on the application's reservation system.
- Used Storybook.is to create self-documenting components in isolation.
- Implemented feature for subscription membership using Redux and calculated reservation payment based on user membership status.
- Refactored existing components to minimize code duplication and styled screens to design specifications.

# VINEYARD SUSTAINABILITY COORDINATOR

Benziger Family Winery / Glen Ellen, CA / 2016-2017

Biodynamic Winery in Sonoma Valley producing premium-quality Bordeauxstyle wines.

- Collected and analyzed vineyard data to monitor vine growth and fertility status.
- Managed greenhouse and insectary gardens, including propagation, irrigation, fertilization and pest control.

#### CO-FOUNDER/MANAGER

Green Almond Farm / Winters, CA / 2014-2016

Organic vegetable farm marketing to high-end Bay Area restaurants.

- Managed crop production for 1.5 acres of certified-organic vegetables.
- Led produce sales to Bay Area restaurants and managed customer relations.